[Music]
yeah dude yawns going ham on Twitter
I'm so happy part of you wants to send
him an email and be like bro you're
totally doing the right thing
thank you thank you for speaking truth
thank you
we don't do that you know talk about
Tommy I'm ice cream on these streams
obviously my personal views are not the
company's views comedy I does not share
those views on incredib I don't have a
person in Twitter but we did you know to
boost our support you wanna lose tough
times along I will say this have you
ever hear this history will remember you
very well history remember you was a
great
you just made your first fork ever man I
don't have any for I have a knife
welcome back think we huh
oh no reddit has lost interest Neil
almost officially I don't like the tires
your top side toward you'd make millions
I don't know I couldn't get through it
looked into Canada's yesterday wooden
Elon do to make me happy this you know
like there's this whole myth that like
the hospitals are like oh my god see
this is the models I was looking for
yesterday that's Rihanna's Twitter
so what did he want do you know he like
geese turn up to people like you know
[Laughter]
[Music]
doesn't have clothes smoking pot Jerry
you know what should we give a little
high it's my last night in the apartment
should we smoke a little weed pretty
good brother looking pretty good all
right we're gonna we're gonna smoke
alone
go smoke a little weed
we left in the bottle the bowl Argos
probably back fresh bowl now we gonna
wait Lex Freeman went to defend Yvonne
and ended up taking the tweet down Lex
come on man we gotta stand up to these
people you know what it is let's go
let's go let's go Lex fell under the
pressure
where do we have the do we have the
desert screenshot of Lexus deleted tweet
anywhere no next to the super nice guy
he's a super nice guy
no Coronas not fake news but like you
know Lex is a nice guy let's let's just
search quickly and say we're gonna find
going on Twitter is this gonna be the
first get high and go on Twitter stream
I don't pull the Elan I'll lose hope
no no no chump chump goes to fly man
chump you know I watch oh we're talking
we really would get high we're going on
Twitter talking about Trump is that
really what we're gonna do you look at
Trump in the primaries and you see him
punch of the Republican guys you know
when Tony chose punching at Jeb Bush Jeb
he put the exclamation point on the end
you know cuz everyone knows how boring
he is he tried to put the exclamation
point to make it less boring but he's no
boring and that's funny all right
and then like I just punch in Hillary
Clinton dude all right I mean it's a
cheap shot but like dude this is the
Clintons but then he becomes president
and keeps punching
[Music]
all right now that's that's it did you
know every time every time they're
thinking about Trump he's it's a small
victory for him people get so butthurt
about him I think he's got a funny but
yeah I imagine trying to be in the way
this is going on to shut down anyone who
has a different opinion audio clip from
YouTube now but you know what I texted I
texted Alex this morning and I said the
internet it's gonna become cool again
because once like YouTube Facebook and
Reddit censor everything like who's
gonna be left on the Internet all the
noobs
and all the people who remind smart can
go form the ultimate man the alternate
Internet's gonna be for a while they're
good for all have them tell all the
noobs come from the internet and then
come to the alternate internet
censorship around here no like you don't
have the alternate alternate in them
it'll be great Conde Nast okay people
think of reddit is like oh it's this
it's just like hip site made by three
guys in San Francisco it's owned by
these people a global mass media company
founded in 1909
we got a fact check yes I'll became an
independent subsidiary of Han yang conde
nast publications subsidiary
okay boom yeah the new search engine you
know I'm going to start a startup and
our mission is going to be to organize
the world's information and I'm gonna
have like ball pits and chefs and it's
all gonna be sick
yeah read it read it lost the iron
Schwartz cultural ago any viable
alternatives to Twitter and reddit not
that I've really seen icy bitch shoot
showing up as an alternative for YouTube
I think gab is its to ten years with
terribleness to be a real alternative to
Twitter the same thing with the votes
the bitch you I don't know I mean it's
it's bad if you go to the homepage
yeah all right I'm hoping some like like
legitimate creators start going over to
bitch you there's this whole joke of
like so you know you do a witch hunt
right and you kick a whole bunch of
people off and they all go we're gonna
go to the new platform and you know the
new platform has three civil
libertarians on it and 97 witches
[Music]
introvert videos that nonsense for
videos I should be able to solve the
talax problem what's the college
problems in Cosmo we're being
open-minded about new ideas can I
suggest anti-aging research hey Jake is
a humanitarian disaster that kills as
many people as World War two every two
years yeah bro thumbs up we like the
talent that's what he says
god no really we're getting high we're
talking about Elon and Trump and Twitter
and the alternative internet it's going
on part right now bro y'all rich
rich rich I don't know I don't know
about Gavin no dad I've just seen some
screenshots when I'm vote briefie let's
see let's see what's on
vocht have your say oh well that's wait
really
I hate when they do this I was looking
at some of the porn alternatives to
tumblr today I was like BDSM LR there
was another one and they both had login
gates why do they do that registration
takes ten seconds if you're yvonne right
now just-just-just if you're either on
right now you're you're sitting there I
think you want owns like what percent of
Tesla does Ilana twenty percent
so if Tesla goes up eight percent and
Elon owns 20% we're doing four cents
right tonight Wow you don't just made
2.3 billion dollars you've looked at
zero that
oh yeah I think I don't know
who's even buying Tesla during tourism
all right we're gonna try to figure out
why oh my god nom too high to do this
voice no no we're not we're not we're
not too high we cannot no should we do
easy stuff what do you want guys want to
do instead we camped a museum easier
it's too hard right now also I've been
doing this all day at work let me
see how see how my dynamics models
learning learning oh god it's not even
up to testing if I did the yeah I wrote
this was one of this day at work so I've
been playing with models all day today
we're tournament dynamics models for
driving pretty cool look at the grooves
man big bruise this is ton awaits
yeah I hope that's how the so many
lawsuit is remembered as that as it just
track just Sony where's your
diss track that's right bitch if you
guys alright I'm taking suggestions so
you can't do anything hard sorry there's
no Museum tonight it's my last night in
the apartment let's get high let's drink
coffee maybe we'll have some some bud
light's I think I got a few last Bud
Lights in the fridge how much did the
Sony lawsuit cost me so I got donations
and I had money left over I have like
seven grand left over so I donated ten
grand to the e FF so of my money it cost
me three thousand dollars and didn't
even have to I just kind of was like I
felt kind of bad like taking donations
but you know Bernie Sanders took
donations but I got my refund so we're
good what good seats yet no no we're not
doing we're not doing CD f's how often
do I usually smoke every other week
every other week at San Francisco I
think I smoked more drank less men in
suits who follow me yeah no they had a
private eye all right this is this is
the smoking weed stream man this is the
smoking weeds Jay now the security
clearance yeah I wouldn't I wouldn't
trust me with the security clearance
prank call some people
yo yo is your refrigerator running
yeah cuz I'm moving out of my apartment
tomorrow and I was just wondering I got
some like food and I was wondering if I
could keep in your fridge rater alright
yeah that's good to know I thank you bye
oh that's a good pretty well it was a
prank
oh I was supposed to your stocks up man
your stocks up but you know
what's up even more
Bitcoin and you know what that means you
don't wait is gold up to Gold's not up
that much wait
Gold's up I don't know I can't we know
Gold's down but that's up from like last
time I looked at it can I see this over
like wow gold is up damn the US dollar
has lost 5x of its value since 2000 but
I'm having is they happening soon should
do viewer Skype Falls I always had up to
do viewer Skype calls I don't know if
we're set up to do viewer Skype calls
let me say no but I have to give you
guys my Skype use discord yeah yeah I
could do it in this cooker just created
this cord now when I creating a
discord no discord that was a
dupe I know your dupe
okay here's what we're gonna do whoo
easy you'd think it would be to build an
app how easy you think it'll be to build
an app where you guys can stream let's
do it let's see if we're gonna build the
app that we use over that time I learned
to react on the stream and then forgot
I'll react
no I said it can't be called app it has
to be called voice app yo this is my new
six startup can you guys check it's
trademarked it's just you're gonna go to
Voice app calm and you're gonna be able
to talk with people right away no
they're not a voice that's gonna be so
secure all right um oh man okay what
language we're gonna write this in
JavaScript voice record using recorder
JX
in the media stream recording API no we
have to figure out okay how do they do
twitch tag top whatever I did for twitch
tactile we want stuff similar to that Oh
simple skills Sunday I remember that
remember this voice all right we're just
gonna call it but maybe Pierre jsr what
spear J ass it sounds good I just let's
let's hear a buzz words my new startup a
simple peer-to-peer with WebRTC
oh yeah yeah this is what we're
talking about all right
media calls oh my god this is so great
this looks so easy oh I use Pierre jf
didn't I use Pierre Jay asked for this I
used pure jazz for this denied yes
this one we're not gonna write a react
we need a server or can I like grant the
permissions to localhost simple
peer-to-peer call answer I said one of
you guys is gonna have to write the call
side of this thing
alright because I'm not gonna post this
on github and it's gonna be the first
person who actually manages to figure
out how to write the other side of this
that will get to come on voice yep well
we're not doing new video show stream in
some video canvas element probably an
example for this
Pierre call another peers ID so wait I
should I print out my Pierre ID that's
answering the call so while I'm
answering the call you guys are gonna
have to call me and figure this out I
think I printed my PR ID I kinda
remember this stuff in twitch pact oh
wow it's so easy how you just don't
remember this well I have to make a new
Pierre I guess so I can say HTML
this state here dot on pier dot on yeah
we'll put that here what is it my app
work I worked really hard on this app I
understand them to my twelve year olds
give up on web oh it's done all right
cool
okay so this is my peer ID you guys
whoever figures out how to call me first
I just will find well right call that
HTML and me out there well you know what
let's make them plot it wants to make it
it has to be a text box import text box
HTML 5 geo do they still have a
w3schools yeah yeah w3schools type of
deep balls man
oh you know what is all this type
equals text
types of callings oh we should put the
game after looks better I now have an
input equals equals we should make it
say after how are we gonna have text oh
yeah beautiful
okay so now we just have to make a
function call at all and we is calling
bro alright now we have to oh man
yo I could use some jQuery right now dot
txt holy person yeah we're gonna use
proper very person to call he is callin
bro undefined it's not dot txt no dot
value it's gotta be value I think it's
value is value yeah okay cool wow that's
loud alarm
is the answer and my name is Khan 8g to
checkmate 5-0 anyone in Chad Nanako
daredevil yo this is this is dumb
man
this is dumb hey alright let's go
let's go we got Voice app over here here
yo who's ready to who wants to invest in
the startup I don't know how you can
invest or what you get but mmm this
isn't good this isn't good guys our
valuations going down illegal invitation
any video videos too much too much
is that why it was an illegal invocation
illegal invocation and calls
wait I don't even have getusermedia do I
have this yes oh no I'm in chromium it's
a good browser the one time it's
appropriate to talk about browsers call
illegal invocation and caught tight
there
what
regal invocation when using media good
catch we'll fix the examples by the way
this is still an issue in the media
section oh we have to bind it to
something what that looks like some
lame-ass JavaScript oh yeah use my
microphone cool ok here is not defined
good that's a good at all good damage
well good damage I we got the new answer
ready to go here is not defined we've
got to make a new peanut in the we is
fallen bro function yeah is this I
something happens I don't know show
stream in some video canvas element this
is probably the hard part
no but seriously if you guys want to
invest in this you can't because just a
great idea it's called voice app it's
gonna be the easiest way to voice
somebody ever let's think of it like a
cell phone but for your web browser yeah
it's a cell phone for your web browser
okay well good we fixed that bug gone
then we're fixing so many bugs okay show
stream in some video elements audio
element the audio embed element yo are
you telling me VoIP okay audio element
from a stream what is a remote stream
media stream html5
you know make me a cellphone and do my
HTML code that's the line I was thinking
about okay good
get audio tracks media track Chanel find
media stream audio element that captures
the stream but we want to do it the
other way we went off on capture a
stream whoa
WebRTC examples streamed stream from a
video element to a peer connection dude
WebRTC is crazy who's ever working on
this stuff you guys are the the people
we need fire RTC comm what I have to
create an account that's too hard I
can't do that this is why we don't know
what's on vote because we didn't create
an account get user media like gaining
access to an input device oh this is too
hard they need to make this stuff easier
man you know we just got our seed round
PHAs audio call example yeah they have
an example Oh perfect a tutorial they
only made it way too complicated now
playing the audio Wow oh yeah window
create object URL oh yeah let's just
let's just steal this I don't will not
forget this time myspace set no paste
what if we just call on receive stream
failed to execute create object URL no
that didn't work
wait what is document query selector
though this is a not we want on receive
call all that answer media straight
answering call started on receive stream
call dot on stream on receive stream I
think that we're gonna have to create an
audio yeah
oh look at that audio you're an answer
you'll always be an answer failed to
execute create object URL audio source
well if I just set the source just
stream am I crazy for thinking this is
gonna work that's how I would have
implemented it file not found object
media stream that's the lamest
I've ever seen that just turned it into
a string okay well you can't just type
in string there you've learned our
lesson show stream in some video canvas
oh well my tutorial go for noob
get user media create object URL I mean
it seems like it's the right idea
no functional to execute create object
URL and URL no function was found that
matched the only thing he provided wave
the lower consider avoiding create
object Oh source object oh that makes
sense
oh yeah that's so sensible yes wow
that's a brilliantly designed API by
super smart people yes we'd love
JavaScript yes I don't know it's
actually probably 2i yeah okay who's
ready to make a call with Voice app we
just put it on github know how else to
do anything how do I host a single page
HTML site easily we have the posting
single page oh my god three dollars a
month I can't afford that
open file upload know what I want
Geocities ya know gh-pages yeah yeah if
fire basis is all too hard yeah yeah
github dot I am what if I don't have a
get up no I don't want to use guys stop
it with all his web 2.0 I'm ready
for the web 7.0 which is free from
censorship yeah I know it's a setting on
the repo yeah it's simple HTTP server
you'll host on your Raspberry Pi okay
bro you got to tell me an IP address and
home that tatak to you you tell me where
your Raspberry Pi is I'll netcat of you
and then you can host them and first off
why - ugly tabs in my way to kind
of start up it's already using tabs over
here at Voice app voice app wait no no
no no no honestly guys what we're
messing this is this is a legitimate
startup here we need we need really to
sell it we need to do a better job
selling this it's um voice app note the
caps is the revolution revolutionary way
I gotta spell it right
revolutionary yes perfect revolutionary
way to all people without censorship or
government injure interfere
it is HTTP I think
so only only top-tier agencies can
listen listen to your calls or maybe
maybe even day camps you missed around
go by voice at all right neck pad who's
guy who's guy who's guys what's your
port give me a URL bro give me a URL and
ikat it right to you put in P and add
title oh yeah we definitely need a title
okay fine I'll put in a P now we got
these do I need to put a title in ahead
I think I might need to put a title in
head title voice app is phone calls
oh wait none of them I'm gonna hang on
hang on hang on I'm forgetting I'm
forgetting a key part of a startup we
have two virtue signal about the good
we're doing for society voice app can be
used by corrupt people in banana
republics man I'm really not good at
this
definitely when I not USA for planning
revolution yes okay that's good good
good oh yes planning revolution powered
by AI what else we got
what else we got served on Ice Age oh I
like that better powered by AI donation
male 2 need some burrs and make it cold
no actually I got a better idea for
we're gonna send our donations no that's
good yeah I all right cool
what else we got alright what else we
got evolution powered by AI and not so
much so much blockchain anymore anymore
but crypto is okay I know I sweet we got
in that kind of alright we're gonna
knock that out I'm excited
thank you we will wait no no don't tell
me
oh man okay you know what we need to put
this in
[Music]
wait I can't access your computer ought
to get four it's off my bra oh yeah chip
the height change you've not my dream
boy Trey let's do it wait surged on sa
put a surge that sa and did your net
that work yet static web publishing oh
oh I kind of like this I mean it
probably is gonna have to install
seventeen million things but ok nvm it's
fall global search I like it I like it
no I have to use a email and
password and look it's gonna download 70
million yo gifts subs who's been gifted
subs it's open start again nan Fox thank
you for subscribing who else subscribed
let me know if you subscribed
oh yo no actually I want to say you
right the way that you said it in all
caps was really inspiring planning
revolution a ipod startup and not much
blocking anymore after I lost all my
house and bit connect ok that's that's
that's the top tier
yeah try your netcat alright our depth
our blinking white silence China's neck
out who can get a neck out to work guys
you got it you should pay attention now
because these are the censorship
resistant tools after youtube's only
gonna let you stop Oh what no what that
is
who's Walter O'Brien all right we got a
new netcat Cano you guys open a
port or can I not open a for it this is
my fault
refresh your fbk what's an fpk you just
sent me a message I don't have an f PK a
Facebook you think I'll go oh
refresh my FB k oh yeah oh sweet
if somebody else's somebody about to
call me wait my Fuhrer just froze up I
was weird I think they're trying to spy
on me for building censorship resistant
tools to allow people wait no but you
can't DDoS my call because it only
accepts one call who's Walter O'Brien I
[Laughter]
don't know what he did
I'm not even gonna I don't even know I
can't even assess the truth of that
right now wait can we not host a webpage
anywhere okay do we need to write a
bootloader let's write a bootloader hang
on hang on hang on I'm gonna write a
bootloader give me a second whoo loader
dot html' all right you're gonna have to
type in bootloader okay we're gonna
write a minimum thing that loads and
executes arbitrary you can host it you
just don't want to put your IP in the
chat I don't know who can host it man
yeah that should open a port but you
have to make sure that your ports open
to the Internet
so if you're like behind a router we got
to get around
zero-zero webhost i come on there's got
to be something that's just gonna let me
upload stuff free web posts you know i
don't want to have to login no this is
something that they can take away cuz
it's censorship
let's try search maybe search will work
search by entering in an email and
password no Leno calm at all alright
that's my project nonchalant volcano oh
wait
Serge is sick well that was amazing
here you go boys alright I'm creating
the new thing first person to call first
person to type it in and call let's go
Serge is amazing
let's go uh-oh we got multiple calls
here hello hello oh I think we have to
stop it from getting hung up no no no we
got to prevent it from getting calls we
use getting calls we have to have accept
call how do i do prompting JavaScript
its prompt you'll be able to call in a
minute don't worry don't worry we got it
we got to add some new functionality but
it's only on there this side so we don't
have to update the page prompt okay why
why prompt your answer if Y y equals
equals yes
but actually is it gonna not be able to
do prompt because that's in a alright
try this one boys it's hosted on Serge
Sh you answer yes hello is there a
person there no hello okay only one
person can call I don't know why it
doesn't work let's just try it here
hopefully again hello yeah it works
locally I think the problem is that
we're just getting so much spam maybe
you answer is the wrong idea maybe we
just need to make it the first one
you're on oh yeah it should be for subs
only that's right make it confirm you
have called that's right
I hated that anyway this is why we use
yet because okay
looks we got to fix this PJs
answer
hello
is there a person
I can kind of hear you
hello
permission just missed Oh No hello is
that a person test yes yo I hear you
yeah it's a Pingree on through you Pig
we don't ones we gain congratulations
welcome you're the first person who
managed to use voice app which voice app
is the revolutionary way to call people
without censorship or government
interference this is a totally safe
phone call we can talk about whatever we
want nobody can listen in the street see
you thank you goodbye
we're taking the next call if anyone
wants to call in and ask me all I have
surrounding your problems we got it the
next call coming in is that a call
hello I'm gonna give everyone a little
bit of time this seems to actually work
okay just a lot of people don't seem
that working mics on their computer hey
do you hear me yeah I can hear you oh
wow sweet gets brings the delaine's
in this question delay yeah yeah can you
hear me friend they're from the app is
voice calls yawns that's great cuz Voice
app works both ways you can both talk
and be talked to
visionary yo thank you thank you and we
hosted it right here on surge I hope we
don't get censored that's right that's
right we built the decentralizing I
thank you I will take one more call
we'll take one more call
hello
yo that's it boys out I'm done I'm done
nonchalant okay you know that surge that
and sage wow wow that was a lot what a
street
what is the Train boys this is smoking
weed streams this is so dangerous
what's dangerous about it you guys can
use nonchalant volcano for all your for
all your needs
all right that's the stream good night I
don't think we can top that I think for
a short stream that's some quality stuff
we're gonna name the title well just
keep it as not new zero by maybe other
things I don't even spelled but right
you know I kind of got to pack up this
apartment is it gonna stay on the deal
yellow I hope it blows up now but the
real the real takeaway from this is guys
we're experiencing a minor episode of a
bunch of those people thinking that they
can censor again and to them I say you
have no idea how hopeless what you're
trying to do is because the spirit of
freedom lives strong in every
red-blooded American voice app once they
start bleeping out words in whatsapp you
know Facebook's gonna do it right how
long before you cannot say the word
Twitter on a whatsapp call when
censorship comes you guys know how easy
it is to build censorship resistant
tools don't ever forget that you saw
this here tonight don't ever forget when
they are when they're taking this stuff
down from YouTube and you know it's only
gonna get worse man the dominoes once
one of them falls they all start falling
but you guys know that I give each and
every one of you permission to be free
if PJs shits on the PJs servers or if
searched on Sh shuts down voice half is
over we ran out of funding I'm sorry we
paid all our money and taxes I don't
know what to tell you
but you know just keep the spirit of
freedom alive and keep the spirit of
hacking alive that shit's the real
spirit of hacking man you know hacking
has nothing to do with computer security
the hacking is it's like a culture
computer security was this thing that
existed for a small period of time there
were plenty of hackers before buffer
overflows existed and it will be plenty
of hackers where a buffer overflows
after the days that buffer overflows
only exists in the past because
everybody is programming in the memory
safe language of rust hack the planet
hack the planet you know hacking is an
idea man and what's at the end of I'm
just I'm not gonna read the whole thing
I'll just read the last I'm a hacker and
this is my manifesto you may stop this
individual but you can't stop us all
after all we're all alike good night
everybody